ecobuild.co.uk 2017-06-20

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy governs the collection and use of personal information by UBM EMEA. For more information about UBM please see: [www.ubm.com](http://www.ubm.com/)

We are committed to abiding by this privacy policy, as well as the requirements of applicable laws, in the operation of our business. Please read this policy carefully as it explains the kinds of personal information we collect about you and how it is handled. By accessing or browsing our websites, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **"Act"** ), the data controller is UBM (UK) Ltd of 240 Blackfriars Road, London SE1 8BF. 

## **COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you access and browse our websites (including when you register for an event or fillin forms on our websites) and when you correspond with us by phone or email, you may give us information about yourself. This information can include your name, payment processing information, postal address, email address, landline and/or mobile telephone number, delivery deails, dietary and access requirements and information about your employment (including your job title, responsibilities and employer's details) as well as other personal information.

With regard to each of your visits to our website(s), we may also collect the following information:

  * technical inforamtion, including the Internet protocal(IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating systems and platforms; and
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstreams to, through and from our websites, products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from that page and any phone number used to call us

We may receive information about you from other websites operated by the UBM group or from the other services that we provide. We also work closely with third parties such as payment processors and app providers and may receive information about you from them.

##  **COOKIES**

Our websites use cookies to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the websites and also allows us to improve our websites. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, please see our cookie policy at <http://privacypolicy.ubm.com/cookiepolicy/>

## **OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use the personal information that you provide to us to provide goods and services to you (including to ensure that your requirements are met at events and to complete any bookings that you make through our website(s) and to process payments as requested by you.

From time to time, we may contact you (or permist selected third parties to contact you) to tell you about our special offers and other goods or services. By providing us with your email address and/or mobile telephone number, you are consenting to us contacting you by email and/or SMS. Third parties will only contact you by electronic means if you have consented to this.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server or to administer our websites. We may conduct analyses of user traffic to measure the use of our websites and to improve our content of our websites and our services. 

If you chose to activate one of the apps available at many of our events, we may use location data from your use of the app to assess how people have moved through the event. 

We also process your personal information where we are required to do so by law and for the exercise or defence or legal claims.

##  **TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share your personal information with any member of the UBM group of companies, which means UBM (UK) Ltd, our subsidiaries and our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 Companies Act 2006. 

We may disclose your personal information to selected third parties outside UBM including for processing purposes associated with payment processing, the supply of goods and services, for web site administration, or elsewhere when you have consented to such disclosures. These third parties are contractually bound only to use personal information to perform the services that we hire them to provide. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective sellter or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if any member of the UBM group or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or in order to enforce our terms and conditions or other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of the UBM group

If you use one of our virtual products, e.g. Virtual Exhibitions, Directory Sites, Webinars etc, we may pass the information you provide to third parties. Generally this will be via a process whereby you, as the user, visit or interact with a third party e.g. visit a stand at an online exhibition or click on an asset branded and provided by a third party. In some instances, for example, a products listing site, you may reach out directly to a supplier or exhibitor who may contact you in return. In other instances our virtual products are sponsored and, in such cases the data you provided to us will be given to the sponsor. Generally, we will let you know at the time of collection, if a product is sponsored. If you wish to change your contact preferences with an individual exhibitor/sonsor, please follow their own unsubscribe request details. Unsubscribing with UBM (UK) Ltd will stop UBM (UK) Ltd from contacting you in the future, but not the individual 3rd parties whom you have interacted with.

##  **WHERE WE STORE YOUR DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of services to you or the processing of your payment details. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot gaurantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

##  **SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use administrative, technical, and physical measures to safegaurd personal information against loss, theft and unauthorised uses, access or modifications. 

Certain areas of our websites may be password protected. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your passwords(s) with anyone. 

Payments made via our websites are processed in a secure environment using software provided by third party providers.

##  **THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND APPS**

Our websites may contain links to and from third party websites and we may provide you with details of apps provided by third parties. Please note that if you follow a link to any of these websites or download an app, these websites and apps will have their own terms of use and privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility of liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites or apps. 

## **YOUR RIGHTS**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. An access request may be subject to a fee (currently Â£10) to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

You also have the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you by contacting us as detailed below. 

## **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at our sole discretion, without prior notice to you. Please review our privacy policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your personal information. Your continued use of our services or our websites following the posting of changes to these terms means that you consent to those changes. 

## **CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can email us at [ubmidpa@ubm.com](mailto:ubmidpa@ubm.com)

  **This version of the privacy policy is effective as of 6 th April 2017**
